Guide to the Communications Workers of America, Local 1032 Records WAG.128
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Communications Workers of America, Local 1032 Records
1978-1995
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Communications Workers of America. Local 1032 (Ewing, N.J.)
Marketti, Jim
WAG.128
25 Linear Feet in 25 record cartons
CWA Local 1032 represents about 6,000 workers in a variety of professions and fields in New Jersey state government (especially the Department of Transportation), the Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, several New Jersey towns and counties as well as several private sector work sites. Headquartered in Ewing, Local 1032 also has offices in Newark and Newton. The records of CWA Local 1032 document the activities of an important New Jersey local. Executive Board material, including minutes, is especially valuable for understanding 1032. Other material in the collection includes organizing campaign files, correspondence, negotiation files, political campaign files, and grievances.
Scope and Content Note
The records of CWA Local 1032 document the activities of an important New Jersey local. Executive Board material, including minutes, is especially valuable for understanding 1032. Other material in the collection includes organizing campaign files, correspondence, negotiation files, political campaign files, and grievances.
Arrangement
This collection has not been arranged by an archivist.
Historical/Biographical Note
CWA Local 1032 represents about 6,000 workers in a variety of professions and fields in New Jersey state government (especially the Department of Transportation), the Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, several New Jersey towns and counties as well as several private sector work sites. Headquartered in Ewing, Local 1032 also has offices in Newark and Newton. Although most of the Local's membership is from New Jersey, some hail from New York.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Jim Marketti, on behalf of the Communications Workers of America, Local 1032, in 2000. The accession number associated with this gift is 1987.014
Custodial History
The archived website was migrated from the California Digital Library's Web Archiving Service to the Internet Archive's Archive-It Service in November 2015. The link to California Digital Library was removed in October 2017.
New Jersey |x Politics and government.; Labor unions |z New Jersey.; New Jersey. Dept. of Transportation; Port Authority of New York and New Jersey; Marketti, Jim; Communications Workers of America. Local 1032 (Ewing, N.J.)
- Budget Proposals, Membership Status, H.M.O. Files, Union Feedback, Meetings for Branch 5, Job Postings, Membership Mailings and Updates, Minority Group Information, National Rainbow Coalition, New Jersey Industrial Union Council, Local Modification Forms, Union Feedback, 1983-1988 (Box 1)
- Correspondence, Executive Board Material (including minutes) (most of the box), New Jersey Legislature Files, Handwritten Notes, Pamphlets, 1983-1988 (Box 2)
- Shop Steward Mailings, D.O.T. General Correspondence, Dental Plan, Women's Committee, Clothing Allowance, CWA Files, Membership Materials, MLO - 109's, Meeting Reports, Conferences and Seminars, 1981-1985 (Box 3)
- Union Activity Leave, General Correspondence, American Income Life, TARLAU, Bonuses, Branch Presidents' Mailings, Bargaining, Benefits, Shop Steward Training, Local 1032 Mailings, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
- Unit Changes, Executive Board Meeting and Minutes, Drop-Outs, ATT&T Files, Office Equipment Info and Catalogues, New Members, Bargaining, Correspondence, Handwritten Notes, 1982-1989 (Box 5)
- Local 1032 Pins & Stickers, Budgetary Files, Correspondence, Questionaires and Reports, Funding, Legal Material -- re: Monmouth County Court Clerks, Handwritten Notes, Surveys, Fliers, 1990-1995 (Box 6)
- Legal Correspondence re: Appeal, Handwritten Notes, Fliers and Pamphlets, Newspapers and Newspaper Clippings, Budgetary Files, Draft Proposals, 1986-1987 (Box 7)
- Individual Files, Correspondence, Reports, Press Releases, Petty Cash Charts, Hay System, Dental Informations. OTIS, PERC Appeals, DOT Policy, Demands and Return System, Newsletters, New Member Files, MLO 109's, Parties, Picnics, and Events, 1983-1987 (Box 8)
- Local Meetings, Membership Mailings, Legal Correspondence, Handwritten Notes, Individual Files, 1985-1987 (Box 9)
- Correspondence, Leaflets, Budgetary Files, Shop Steward Training Materials, Individual Files, Bulletins, Mailings, and Newsletters, Handwritten Notes, Draft Statements, Pamphlets and Booklets, CWA Agreements, 1983-1986 (Box 10)
- Executive Board Meeting Minutes, C.O.P.E. Correspondence, Conference For Public Health Care Files, Conventions, Seminars, Conferences, Local Meeting Materials and Fliers, Worksite Notices for various Branches, UCLEA Summer Institution, Handwritten Notes, 1986-1988 (Box 11)
- Correspondence, Membership Lists, Payroll, Handwritten Notes, Budgetary Concerns, Retiree Files, Data Processing, Trust Fund, Pamphlets, Pins, and Public Material, Staff Meeting Minutes, Union Activity Leave, Branch 7 Meeting Notices, Conferences, Conventions, and Seminars, District Leadership, District Legislative Files, 1987-1988 (Box 12)
- Mailings, Fliers, Newspaper Clippings, Political Cartoons, Correspondence with Handwritten Notes, Newsletters, CWA Organization Charts, AFL Materials, Newspapers, 1986-1995 (Box 13)
- Welfare Contracts, Correspondence, Mailings, Budget and Disbursement Files, Discrimination Materials, Branch 8, MCDSS Negotiations, Handwritten Notes, 1990-1993 (Box 14)
- Discrimination Material, Correspondence, Handwritten Notes, Subcontracting, On the Move Files, Individual Files, Shop Steward Training, Shop Steward Submissions, Newspapers and Newspaper Clippings, Wage Demands, General Union Files, AGRE, Worksite Notices Branch 5, Access Letters, 1981-1986 (Box 15)
- Executive Board Meeting Minutes, Incoming Mail, Correspondence, Health & Safety Reports and Regulatory Files, Vision Care, CWA Fact Sheets, Newspaper Clippings, Health and Safety Fliers, Leaflets, Health and Safety Conference, Meetings, and Committee, 1987-1990 (Box 16)
- Fliers, Mailings, Leaflets, Advertisements, Material from Other Locals, Newspapers and Newspaper Clippings, Correspondence re: Events and Demonstrations, Pamphlets, 1987-1991 (Box 17)
- Handwritten Notes, Charts, Fliers, Correspondence, Roundtable Discussion Materials, Policies and Reports re: Health and Safety, Political Correspondence, Pay Equity, Budget Statistics, Payroll, Salaries, Budget Files and Administrative Materials, Overtime for FLSA, Pamphlets and Newsletters, Newspapers and Newspaper Clippings, Mailings, 1986-1988 (Box 18)
- Handwritten Notes, Distribution Materials, Correspondence, Organizing Materials, IAQ Buttons and Stickers, Advisory Board Materials, Organizational Reports, Newspaper Clippings, Newsletters, Health Department Files, Administrative Regulations, Background Materials to PEOSHA, Union Committee, VDT Bill, 1987-1994 (Box 19)
- Classification, Certification, Civil Service, Correspondence, Legal Dockets, Department Personnel Activities, Overtime Rules and Regulations, Salary, Principal Drafting Tech Exam, Salary Administrative Regulations, Civil Service Reform, State Promotional Announcements and Procedure, Labor Advisory Board, Newspaper Clippings, 1983-1988 (Box 20)
- Buttons, Pins, Stickers, Ribbons, Correspondence, IP Charges, Legal Memoranda, Pamphlets, Handwritten Notes, Forms and Reports, Judicial Takeover Papers, Requests and Appropriation Forms, Past Election Forms and Old Campaigns, 1978-1993 (Box 21)
- Legal Correspondence, Complaints, Court Files, Legal Review Articles, News Articles, Handwritten Notes, Contract Proposals, 1989-1991 (Box 22)
- Mobilizing Pamphlets, Franklin Services, Handwritten Notes, Correspondence, Legal Materials, CWA Ribbons, Agreement, Contract Proposal, Contract Ratification, Internal Memoranda -- West Windsor Township, Legal Mailings, Organizing Drive Materials, 1980-1993 (Box 23)
- Correspondence, Negotiation Files, Grievances, and Contracts Relating to Skeist Incorporated, Trenton Academy Day Care Center, and J. August's Cafe. Also Includes Diane Snyder Files and General Material (Pamphlets, Fliers, Mailings, Buttons and Pins, Legal Briefs, Survey Information, Membership Cards, Newsletters, Reports, Child Care Listings), 1983-1992 (Box 24)
- Advisory Board Materials, Pamphlets and Publications, Handwritten Notes, Newspaper Clippings, Inter Local Health and Safety Meeting Material, Correspondence and Draft, Standard VDTs, Hazard Waste Reports, Institutional Employer Health and Safety Reports, Agenda for Public Employees Occupational Safety, IAQ Standard -- New Jersey, 1987-1992 (Box 25)
- Archived Website, Feb 26, 2009-ongoing
  Scope and Content Note
  Communications Workers of America Local 1032 represents about 6,000 workers in a variety of professions and fields in several New Jersey State Departments, the Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, several New Jersey towns and counties as well as several private sector work sites.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.